[Music]
hello everyone and welcome back to my
channel random facts by shikha
so in today's video we will know top 10
best general insurance companies in
india
[Music]
if code tokyo was incorporated in the
year 2000
and is headquartered in gurkham haryana
it
offers insurance services in motor
health
travel home and in a lot more places
reliance general insurance company is an
indian private insurance company
and is headquartered in mumbai
[Music]
hdfc general insurance was founded in
the year 2002
and is headquartered in mumbai it is a
joint venture firm between the hdfc
and ergo international aeg
[Music]
tata aig general insurance company is a
joint venture between the tata group
and american international group it was
founded in the eu 2001
january and is headquartered in mumbai
icici lombard general insurance
companies headquartered in mumbai
and it is engaged in general insurance
insurance claims management
reinsurance and investment management
bajaj alliance general insurance is a
private general insurance company in
india and is headquartered in pune
it is a joint venture between bajaj pin
serve limited
and allianz sc
[Music]
united india insurance company is an
indian leading general insurance company
incorporated on 18
february 1938. it is a fully owned
by government of india and is
headquartered in chennai india
[Music]
the oriental insurance is headquartered
in new delhi
and is a public sector general insurance
company of india which
was founded in september 1947.
[Music]
national insurance india was established
in 1906
and is headquartered in kolkata west
bengal it is the oldest
insurer company in the country
new india assurance was founded in the
year 1919
by sir tarub ji tata and is
headquartered in mumbai maharashtra
it offered insurances in various sectors
like marine
jewelry aviation to name a few
[Music]
do